{"data":[{"question":"We were not happy with the plans________ the architect showed us for our new house. Obviously, he had never designed a home like the one we wanted.","a":"that","b":"in that","c":"in which","d":"who","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use that (pronoun) as the object in the relative clause\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"When I saw that Mike was having trouble, I ________ him. He was very appreciative.","a":"was helping","b":"were helping","c":"helped","d":"help","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (When I saw).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"My wife and I went to Disneyland when we visited Los Angeles last spring. Prior to that time, we ________ to such a big amusement park. It was a lot of fun.","a":"had never been","b":"were never been","c":"never were","d":"were never","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense: expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (Prior to that time).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"Last year I experienced ________ I had flown in an air plane for fairly long distances before, but never as long as when I went to Australia last June.","a":"how can tedious long plane trips be","b":"how tedious can long plane trips be","c":"how long plane trips can be tedious","d":"how tedious long plane trips can be","answer":"4","explain":"\n- How + [adjective\/adverb] + S + V: used to emphasize the quality you are mentioning.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't want you ________ my arriving late.","a":"mention","b":"to mention","c":"mentioning","d":"mentioned","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Want somebody to do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"If you can't unscrew the lid, try ________ it with a hammer.","a":"to hit","b":"hit","c":"hitting","d":"hits","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Try + Verb_ing: to do or use something for a short while to discover if it is suitable, successful, enjoyable.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"I remember ________ him say the grass needed ________ yesterday.","a":"to hear \/ cutting","b":"hearing \/ to cut","c":"hearing \/ cutting","d":"to hear \/ to cut","answer":"3","explain":"- To remember doing something: to have an image in your mind of a person, a place or something that happened or was said in the past\n- Need doing = need to be PII \u00a0(passive meaning)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"I advise you ________ before deciding ________ the job.","a":"waiting \/ accepting","b":"waiting \/ to accept","c":"to wait \/ to accept","d":"to wait \/ accepting","answer":"3","explain":"- Advise\/ allow\/ permit\/ recommend + object + to V.\n- Decide to do sth.\n\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"We regret ________ that the lecture was very dull and wasn't worth ________.","a":"to say \/ to listen to","b":"saying \/ listening to","c":"saying \/ to listen to","d":"to say \/ listening to","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To be worth doing sth.\u00a0\n- Regret+To Verb: Feel sorry for something you are going to do.\u00a0\n- Regret + Verb-ing: Feel sorry or sad that you have said","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"},{"question":"I couldn't resist ________ him why he was trying ________ meeting me.","a":"asking \/ to avoid","b":"asking \/ avoiding","c":"to ask \/ to avoid","d":"to ask \/ avoiding","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Resist doing something.\u00a0\n- Try + To Verb: attempt to do\/make an effort to do.\u00a0\n- Try + Verb_ing: do something as an experiment or test.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"31","type":"1"}]}